Contact

hbochantin@yahoo.com

www.linkedin.com/in/hilma-peiso-bochantin-522b6730 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

BLS

Clinical Research

Healthcare Management

Hilma Peiso Bochantin

MSN, RN, FNP-C, CEN

Houston, Texas Area

Summary

Fluent, bilingual English-Spanish Family Nurse Practitioner with 17 years of RN Emergency/Trauma Nursing experience, who possesses strong clinical and leadership skills, provides evidence based, quality care to diverse populations across the lifespan within a fast-paced practice/clinic/emergency center environment. Flexible, lifetime learner; adapts easily to new situations and enjoys challenge.

Experience

Memorial Hermann Health System Clinical Coordinator October 2016 - Present (3 years 8 months) Houston, Texas Area

Harris Health System
Emergency Room RN
August 2009 - October 2016 (7 years 3 months)

Memorial Hermann Health System
Emergency Room RN
December 2000 - January 2010 (9 years 2 months)

Education

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston Bachelor of Science in Nursing, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse

The University of Texas Health Science Center at Houston (UTHealth)

Master of Science in Nursing, Family Nurse Practitioner